[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "Is it a hate crime?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "hate", "crime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "An action to take like this has to be -- it has to be some form of hate.", "answer_tokens": ["An", "action", "to", "take", "like", "this", "has", "to", "be", "--", "it", "has", "to", "be", "some", "form", "of", "hate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", ",", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Do you -- have you felt like you've been vulnerable?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "have", "you", "felt", "like", "you", "'ve", "been", "vulnerable", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Yes, I think my first reaction was, to be honest with you, I could guess, you know, it was a case of mistaken identity.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "my", "first", "reaction", "was", ",", "to", "be", "honest", "with", "you", ",", "I", "could", "guess", ",", "you", "know", ",", "it", "was", "a", "case", "of", "mistaken", "identity", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "What is your reaction to that statement from the family of the man that committed this terrible atrocity?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "statement", "from", "the", "family", "of", "the", "man", "that", "committed", "this", "terrible", "atrocity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Do you believe that this kind of extremism, the white supremacy, but also other forms of extremism, is that on the increase in America, do you believe?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "this", "kind", "of", "extremism", ",", "the", "white", "supremacy", ",", "but", "also", "other", "forms", "of", "extremism", ",", "is", "that", "on", "the", "increase", "in", "America", ",", "do", "you", "believe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I think there's no question about it at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "no", "question", "about", "it", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "I mean what do you imagine may have been given what you know about his background, his motivation here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "do", "you", "imagine", "may", "have", "been", "given", "what", "you", "know", "about", "his", "background", ",", "his", "motivation", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "My best guess is that he's a fool.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "best", "guess", "is", "that", "he", "'s", "a", "fool", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "What is your recollection of the kind of man that Wade Michael Page was?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "recollection", "of", "the", "kind", "of", "man", "that", "Wade", "Michael", "Page", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "As I recall he was a bright, intelligent, and very kind individual.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "I", "recall", "he", "was", "a", "bright", ",", "intelligent", ",", "and", "very", "kind", "individual", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wade Michael Page"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "I mean, who were the targets of this holy war as far as he was concerned?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "who", "were", "the", "targets", "of", "this", "holy", "war", "as", "far", "as", "he", "was", "concerned", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "Back then, as far as he was concerned, it was just anybody that wasn't white.", "answer_tokens": ["Back", "then", ",", "as", "far", "as", "he", "was", "concerned", ",", "it", "was", "just", "anybody", "that", "was", "n't", "white", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBD", ",", "CC", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Do you know what the details of that misconduct were?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "what", "the", "details", "of", "that", "misconduct", "were", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Basically, it was just -- he had gotten drunk the night before and showed up at morning formation intoxicated, and that just started the ball rolling to get him moved out of the military.", "answer_tokens": ["Basically", ",", "it", "was", "just", "--", "he", "had", "gotten", "drunk", "the", "night", "before", "and", "showed", "up", "at", "morning", "formation", "intoxicated", ",", "and", "that", "just", "started", "the", "ball", "rolling", "to", "get", "him", "moved", "out", "of", "the", "military", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Would he have tried to distinguish between the two groups?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "have", "tried", "to", "distinguish", "between", "the", "two", "groups", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Honestly, I don't think he would have tried to distinguish.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "would", "have", "tried", "to", "distinguish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "Did you come away from that encounter thinking that he was now dangerous and that this was not just talk?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "come", "away", "from", "that", "encounter", "thinking", "that", "he", "was", "now", "dangerous", "and", "that", "this", "was", "not", "just", "talk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "No, I knew that it wasn't just talk, that he had fallen deeper into whatever group he had gotten himself mixed up with.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "knew", "that", "it", "was", "n't", "just", "talk", ",", "that", "he", "had", "fallen", "deeper", "into", "whatever", "group", "he", "had", "gotten", "himself", "mixed", "up", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What is the practical thing that can be done now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "practical", "thing", "that", "can", "be", "done", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Piers, what is really interesting is that my comment that guns don't belong in the civil society generated so much hostility, anger, rage, ethnocentrism, bigotry, prejudice, and racism.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "what", "is", "really", "interesting", "is", "that", "my", "comment", "that", "guns", "do", "n't", "belong", "in", "the", "civil", "society", "generated", "so", "much", "hostility", ",", "anger", ",", "rage", ",", "ethnocentrism", ",", "bigotry", ",", "prejudice", ",", "and", "racism", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Is there so many gun murders as a matter of routine every day, every week, every month, every year?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "so", "many", "gun", "murders", "as", "a", "matter", "of", "routine", "every", "day", ",", "every", "week", ",", "every", "month", ",", "every", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Taliban"]}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "-- fears that maybe it was deliberately targeted at the Sikh community?", "question_tokens": ["--", "fears", "that", "maybe", "it", "was", "deliberately", "targeted", "at", "the", "Sikh", "community", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "He probably assumed that anyone with a beard or a turban is probably from the Taliban.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "probably", "assumed", "that", "anyone", "with", "a", "beard", "or", "a", "turban", "is", "probably", "from", "the", "Taliban", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What was your reaction when that happened to someone so close to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "your", "reaction", "when", "that", "happened", "to", "someone", "so", "close", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "DT", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "RANKLIN: Just complete shock.", "answer_tokens": ["RANKLIN", ":", "Just", "complete", "shock", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "What are you, 17?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", ",", "17", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "It must feels slightly surreal, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "must", "feels", "slightly", "surreal", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "Oh my gosh, without a doubt.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "gosh", ",", "without", "a", "doubt", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Are you all buddies?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "all", "buddies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "My question for you is you could go to a desert island with one of two men, Ryan Lochte or Michael Phelps, for the rest of your life, who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["My", "question", "for", "you", "is", "you", "could", "go", "to", "a", "desert", "island", "with", "one", "of", "two", "men", ",", "Ryan", "Lochte", "or", "Michael", "Phelps", ",", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", ",", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan Lochte", "Michael Phelps"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Why have you done that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "done", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Because I am all about the team.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "am", "all", "about", "the", "team", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Where are you going?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "going", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I have no idea yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Harvard?", "question_tokens": ["Harvard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Probably not.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Do you believe that the achievements of the Jamaican team should be viewed without any suspicion?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "the", "achievements", "of", "the", "Jamaican", "team", "should", "be", "viewed", "without", "any", "suspicion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I certainly don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "certainly", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Do I look gangster?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "look", "gangster", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "Yes --", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Phelps"]}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Who has excited you most watching the other sports?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "has", "excited", "you", "most", "watching", "the", "other", "sports", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "JJS", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Gosh, I can't sit here and not say Michael Phelps.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "sit", "here", "and", "not", "say", "Michael", "Phelps", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "What about Usain Bolt last night?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Usain", "Bolt", "last", "night", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "I was going to get to him too.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "going", "to", "get", "to", "him", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Usain Bolt"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "And more importantly, to be sitting here with me again?", "question_tokens": ["And", "more", "importantly", ",", "to", "be", "sitting", "here", "with", "me", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "JJR", "RB", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"]}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Take me back to that decision?", "question_tokens": ["Take", "me", "back", "to", "that", "decision", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "About 2008, she was about 11, she started saying, mom, I think that I can do this.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "2008", ",", "she", "was", "about", "11", ",", "she", "started", "saying", ",", "mom", ",", "I", "think", "that", "I", "can", "do", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "CC", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Or she's finding a new mother?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "she", "'s", "finding", "a", "new", "mother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "AWKINS: Or that too.", "answer_tokens": ["AWKINS", ":", "Or", "that", "too", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "When she first arrived, what was your first impression?", "question_tokens": ["When", "she", "first", "arrived", ",", "what", "was", "your", "first", "impression", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "She glows when she smiles and she's a doll to be around.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "glows", "when", "she", "smiles", "and", "she", "'s", "a", "doll", "to", "be", "around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "What was the moment like when she won gold?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "moment", "like", "when", "she", "won", "gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "For me, it was just total elation, because I knew what had gone into making that dream come true.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "me", ",", "it", "was", "just", "total", "elation", ",", "because", "I", "knew", "what", "had", "gone", "into", "making", "that", "dream", "come", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VB", "RP", "CC", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Missy, for you?", "question_tokens": ["Missy", ",", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Just so proud of her, to again make all the sacrifices that she made at such a young age, and then go out and live her dream and at the same time representing her country.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "so", "proud", "of", "her", ",", "to", "again", "make", "all", "the", "sacrifices", "that", "she", "made", "at", "such", "a", "young", "age", ",", "and", "then", "go", "out", "and", "live", "her", "dream", "and", "at", "the", "same", "time", "representing", "her", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "That was ridiculous, didn't you think?", "question_tokens": ["That", "was", "ridiculous", ",", "did", "n't", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Could you ever imagine in your wildest dreams this was going to happen to your little girl?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "ever", "imagine", "in", "your", "wildest", "dreams", "this", "was", "going", "to", "happen", "to", "your", "little", "girl", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120806pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WDT", "NNS", "JJS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "How are you going to keep her under control?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "keep", "her", "under", "control", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Right now, we're taking our time to see which brands most are compatible with what she wants to personify.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "now", ",", "we", "'re", "taking", "our", "time", "to", "see", "which", "brands", "most", "are", "compatible", "with", "what", "she", "wants", "to", "personify", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]